Work performance reports.
So we've already
mentioned that we'll put all the
progress together called
work performance information.
What's happening with every aspect of our
project together,
progress to create reports.
Reports go out to stakeholders so that
we're letting them know, communicating
with them what's happening with the
project, right?
So remember that it's only with work
performance.
reports that we raise awareness,
take action, and make decisions.
Because work performance
reports are stating
what's happening with
every aspect of the project.
So if we look at the second slide, examples
of types of work performance reports.
Status reports, where the project
currently stands.
Also progress reports,
what's been accomplished
since the last report that we sent out.
We also will include forecasts for
schedule and calls.
costs.
All right.
So we'll predict either estimate at
completion or estimate to complete.
So those will be discussed in more detail
later.
But estimate at completion, based on our
performance and what we predict think is
going to happen in the future, how
much is the whole project going to cost?
Or how long will the whole project take?
Estimate to complete ETC
from this point forward, how
long will it take us to
finish the remaining work?
How much will it cost us to finish the
remaining work?
So those will be forecasts.
All right.
So types of forecast, you can have time
series, projects based on historical data,
causal econometric forecast based on
causes and events that are happening.
Judgmental, expert judgment.
Others can be simulation, Probabilistic
forecasting.
All right, so types of reports can include
variance reports.
Off are we from our plan?
Remember, we're comparing our plan to
actuals looking for variance.
Variants will say how far off we are.
Trend reports, how we're performing over
time, better or worse, as well as earned
value with the value of the work we've
completed.
Now with Agile, which will be covered in
detail, and I believe we
have examples as well.
You also have burn-up
charts, which will show
the work that's been completed or earned.
Ties right in with earned value.
There's also burned-down charts,
shows the work remaining.
And we can also have velocity,
velocity charts.
This shows how the
team's performing over time
within sprints to help
forecast future performance.
And then con bond boards, the task boards
showing the work and progress,
what needs to be done,
what's in progress, what needs
to be tested, what's been
completed, for example.
All of these are types of reports that
we'll send out to our stakeholders to let
them know what's happening with every
aspect of our project.
So again, remember that reports are used
that we send out to our stakeholders,
communicate out to raise awareness,
take action, and make decisions,
only based on reports.
Thank you.